[{"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120303pmt", "aSentId": 17, "question": "How would you like to play my ex-husband?", "qSentId": 16}, {"answer": "OK.", "docId": "120303pmt", "aSentId": 51, "question": "What made you get up one day and say I'm going to do this?", "qSentId": 50}, {"answer": "I'm driving a cab at night now.", "docId": "120303pmt", "aSentId": 61, "question": "How bad are you going to miss it, Bill?", "qSentId": 60}, {"answer": "Well, no, because it wasn't to him, it was to the super PAC.", "docId": "120303pmt", "aSentId": 72, "question": "Have you heard from the president since your donation?", "qSentId": 71}, {"answer": "It's a silly argument.", "docId": "120303pmt", "aSentId": 80, "question": "Is it a silly argument?", "qSentId": 79}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, he would just -- he would out-and-out lose this election if he didn't -- it is not hypocrisy.", "docId": "120303pmt", "aSentId": 88, "question": "That's still hypocrisy, isn't it?", "qSentId": 87}, {"answer": "Of course, because otherwise he doesn't win.", "docId": "120303pmt", "aSentId": 94, "question": "Even if you think it's morally and ethically wrong?", "qSentId": 93}, {"answer": "Well, that's true.", "docId": "120303pmt", "aSentId": 97, "question": "But given that Romney is outspending all his competitors with these super PACs, and like 10-1 and he still isn't getting very far, certainly not winning his election battle at the moment, what makes you think the super PACs are actually that effective?", "qSentId": 96}, {"answer": "You will try to --", "docId": "120303pmt", "aSentId": 125, "question": "Would every coach do that?", "qSentId": 124}, {"answer": "Of course, every -- they always have.", "docId": "120303pmt", "aSentId": 129, "question": "Would every coach do that?", "qSentId": 128}, {"answer": "But here's the problem.", "docId": "120303pmt", "aSentId": 149, "question": "It's true, when Rick -- when Rick Santorum says, you know, Obama thinks that your -- I don't know what -- what did he say about Obama that he wants to rule over you?", "qSentId": 148}, {"answer": "I don't think he read the speech properly because that's not what Kennedy was saying.", "docId": "120303pmt", "aSentId": 170, "question": "How dare you say you won't be taking your orders from the Pope?", "qSentId": 169}, {"answer": "It's similar to the silly thing about you -- the designated hitter and how that's a hypocrite.", "docId": "120303pmt", "aSentId": 210, "question": "What do you think of that whole argument on both sides?", "qSentId": 209}, {"answer": "Well, sometimes you do need a nanny state.", "docId": "120303pmt", "aSentId": 222, "question": "How much should the government lead, and how much strays into nanny state, do you think?", "qSentId": 221}, {"answer": "I hadn't seen that.", "docId": "120303pmt", "aSentId": 246, "question": "Did you find that funny or not?", "qSentId": 245}, {"answer": "Exactly.", "docId": "120303pmt", "aSentId": 256, "question": "What's to get upset about?", "qSentId": 255}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120303pmt", "aSentId": 260, "question": "You -- was it at the \"Vanity Fair\" party you met Tim Tebow?", "qSentId": 259}, {"answer": "Of course.", "docId": "120303pmt", "aSentId": 265, "question": "Do you like him?", "qSentId": 264}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, it's a joke.", "docId": "120303pmt", "aSentId": 276, "question": "Satan, Hitler?", "qSentId": 275}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120303pmt", "aSentId": 284, "question": "Inspiring?", "qSentId": 283}, {"answer": "If you work from the point of view that most Americans are not atheists like you, then actually, if they do believe in God, having a clean living, superbly talented professional sportsman actually being very, I think, modest, you know, humble --", "docId": "120303pmt", "aSentId": 287, "question": "People who are religious?", "qSentId": 286}, {"answer": "Well, he can.", "docId": "120303pmt", "aSentId": 290, "question": "Why can't he do it with his religion, if he believes?", "qSentId": 289}, {"answer": "ORGAN: And they actually, I suspect, do believe that it's perfectly acceptable for people of religious influence to work in politics as well and govern.", "docId": "120303pmt", "aSentId": 308, "question": "So?", "qSentId": 307}, {"answer": "Of course not.", "docId": "120303pmt", "aSentId": 328, "question": "If Jeremy Lin came to you and said, look, I want you to join me in prayer and I will score 20 more points against the Lakers, would you do it?", "qSentId": 327}, {"answer": "Get on your knees and start praying, Bill Maher.", "docId": "120303pmt", "aSentId": 335, "question": "What?", "qSentId": 334}, {"answer": "My wife called me this morning.", "docId": "120303pmt", "aSentId": 365, "question": "How did you hear the news?", "qSentId": 364}, {"answer": "Well, yes, we were quite good friends.", "docId": "120303pmt", "aSentId": 373, "question": "Were you good friends?", "qSentId": 372}, {"answer": "Oh, I think so, absolutely.", "docId": "120303pmt", "aSentId": 404, "question": "Was he content with his life, do you think?", "qSentId": 403}, {"answer": "It would have been just a few months ago.", "docId": "120303pmt", "aSentId": 428, "question": "When was the last time you spoke to him, Micky?", "qSentId": 427}, {"answer": "Always did -- did all of us, yes.", "docId": "120303pmt", "aSentId": 442, "question": "Did that bring Davy a lot of pleasure, the fact that you guys were back together and getting great reviews and so on?", "qSentId": 441}, {"answer": "One of your quick little things.", "docId": "120303pmt", "aSentId": 486, "question": "What do you want me to do?", "qSentId": 485}, {"answer": "Oh, absolutely, he had family back there.", "docId": "120303pmt", "aSentId": 504, "question": "Did he remain proud of his English roots, Micky?", "qSentId": 503}, {"answer": "Oh, boy, it's a lot.", "docId": "120303pmt", "aSentId": 515, "question": "When you're hearing all the tributes today, Micky, and all the music being played again and so on, what's your abiding memory of Davy Jones?", "qSentId": 514}, {"answer": "Working.", "docId": "120303pmt", "aSentId": 535, "question": "What are you doing?", "qSentId": 534}, {"answer": "I'm too lucky.", "docId": "120303pmt", "aSentId": 545, "question": "I'm going to find out the secrets of the most devilish woman on television?", "qSentId": 544}, {"answer": "That's very true.", "docId": "120303pmt", "aSentId": 568, "question": "You know, back in Britain, you're not that famous, are you?", "qSentId": 567}, {"answer": "When I won the Emmy -- they didn't, when I was nominated, I wasn't on the list.", "docId": "120303pmt", "aSentId": 571, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 570}, {"answer": "I think there's different ways to describe an arranged marriage.", "docId": "120303pmt", "aSentId": 593, "question": "But if you don't like him, you don't have to marry him, is that right?", "qSentId": 592}, {"answer": "We just got on.", "docId": "120303pmt", "aSentId": 599, "question": "How did things develop?", "qSentId": 598}, {"answer": "Well, if you let me talk, Piers.", "docId": "120303pmt", "aSentId": 609, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 608}, {"answer": "She just said, I did introduce you and I say, yes, you did.", "docId": "120303pmt", "aSentId": 615, "question": "Does your mom take all the credit?", "qSentId": 614}, {"answer": "Oh, God, that would be --", "docId": "120303pmt", "aSentId": 618, "question": "Perish the thought?", "qSentId": 617}, {"answer": "To have a little Kalinda.", "docId": "120303pmt", "aSentId": 623, "question": "To have a little Kalinda?", "qSentId": 622}, {"answer": "I know when people say that to me, it doesn't worry me.", "docId": "120303pmt", "aSentId": 632, "question": "But is that -- I mean, how do you feel about becoming 40?", "qSentId": 631}, {"answer": "Very nice woman.", "docId": "120303pmt", "aSentId": 654, "question": "What is she like then, Angie?", "qSentId": 653}, {"answer": "Very nice man.", "docId": "120303pmt", "aSentId": 657, "question": "And brad?", "qSentId": 656}, {"answer": "Occasionally.", "docId": "120303pmt", "aSentId": 659, "question": "Did you all hang out together?", "qSentId": 658}, {"answer": "Stop being so naughty, Piers.", "docId": "120303pmt", "aSentId": 662, "question": "Who rings who?", "qSentId": 661}, {"answer": "No, we don't.", "docId": "120303pmt", "aSentId": 666, "question": "Do you go out and have a few beers?", "qSentId": 665}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120303pmt", "aSentId": 672, "question": "Would I like to be as famous as that?", "qSentId": 671}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120303pmt", "aSentId": 689, "question": "We got a little glimpse of it there, but you put this down to an Indian diet that you had, (INAUDIBLE), right?", "qSentId": 688}, {"answer": "I'm surprised you didn't discover that.", "docId": "120303pmt", "aSentId": 694, "question": "Did they really?", "qSentId": 693}, {"answer": "Terrible.", "docId": "120303pmt", "aSentId": 701, "question": "How did that make you feel as a young man?", "qSentId": 700}, {"answer": "Horrible.", "docId": "120303pmt", "aSentId": 703, "question": "That's awful, isn't it?", "qSentId": 702}, {"answer": "That maybe that was the reason I wasn't giving the roles because I was fine in delivering the dialogue and that maybe a sign I should work on it.", "docId": "120303pmt", "aSentId": 707, "question": "How did you react to this critique from your agent?", "qSentId": 706}, {"answer": "It's very strange watching myself on that, Piers.", "docId": "120303pmt", "aSentId": 711, "question": "So when you now see yourself as this little vamp from \"The Good Wife,\" you must feel pretty good, right?", "qSentId": 710}, {"answer": "Well, sometimes, every time I have other characters, and I come home with my hair and makeup, he's like, take it off because I hate your make up.", "docId": "120303pmt", "aSentId": 716, "question": "What does your husband make of it?", "qSentId": 715}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120303pmt", "aSentId": 732, "question": "How would you like to play my ex-husband?", "qSentId": 731}, {"answer": "I'll speak to the kings.", "docId": "120303pmt", "aSentId": 735, "question": "Are you serious?", "qSentId": 734}, {"answer": "Negotiable.", "docId": "120303pmt", "aSentId": 739, "question": "Are they negotiable?", "qSentId": 738}, {"answer": "Oh, I'm sure -- he's a big fan of yours, I'm sure, he --", "docId": "120303pmt", "aSentId": 741, "question": "How is Raj going to feel about this?", "qSentId": 740}]